MH TUHIN

Address: tongi, satais borobazar., Tongi, Gazipur

Primary Mobile No: 01830879724 Primary Email: rmhtuhin100@gmail.com



Career Objective:

i have did sell marketing job in 8 years. I have top level experience in marketing .Abul Khair, Dekko,

Career Summary:

With 8 years of experience in Sales Marketing and Brand Representative. I started my career in Student Life and have had the opportunity to interact with people from all walks of life through Sales Marketing. I was able to put my brand in their work by understand the testimonies of the people. Understanding people's thoughts and needs by presenting the benefits and advantages of brand to them, by presenting their own practical, aspects to them.

Special Qualification:

presentation making and presenting

Employment History:

Total Year of Experience: 8.8 yrs

1. Researcher (3.9 yrs)

(December, 2018 - Continuing)

Own interest

home

Area of Expertise

realization (3.6 yrs)

Duties/Responsibilities

Dhaka, Bangladesh Doing research is my hobby or desire. I do this from my personal past desire. Personally, I have completed my project by working with people for 5 long years. My research projects are: 1. depression. 2. why do people step on the dark path. 3. children (their mental health). and In addition I have done two more of them. means project complete

2. public Mentor (4.6 yrs)

(April, 2018 - Continuing)

market

Dhaka

Area of Expertise

Team building and leading (4.2 yrs)

Duties/Responsibilities

Bangladesh and social communication From personal life experience and long 5 year work life experience, experience on human life to friends, classmates or the general consumer in the field of work or online media advises different friends. Of any kind. I give advice from my own life and thousands of lives from people's lives, from books, and lessons from history, and when ordinary or young, decent people are happy with my advice, I am very happy and I think, I feel happier than in the world. Do and benefit people's lives.

3. story writer (6.4 yrs)

(June, 2016 - Continuing)

At Home

online

Area of Expertise

Creative Content Creation (5.1 yrs)

Duties/Responsibilities

I studied literature. English Department. So writing stories has become my habit. Whenever I have time I start writing. Such as: plays, pictures, short stories, love stories, real life stories, songs, dialogues. It has become a habit. I write all my stories in Microsoft Office.

4. Executive (0.5 yr)

(May, 2022 - November, 2022)

Akid design and furniture

Mirpur

Area of Expertise

Corporate Agreements (0.5 yr)

Duties/Responsibilities

I am now working at Akid design and furniture. And here, my responsibility is greatly BRprovide service to our corporate client(NUB,DBBL,CRP,RUPAYON,SHERATON,ETC). BRAnd maintain them as our life time client and I have to maintain office work and client and BRmy team.

5. Freelancer (1.7 yrs)

(April, 2019 - December, 2020)

Freelancer

online

Area of Expertise

Data Entry Operator (Both English & Bengali) (1.6 yrs)

Duties/Responsibilities

I needed to work in Microsoft Office, Excel and have practical education. Because I had to work on a computer to keep track of every job. And work on computers to write stories for personal needs. I took computer education in 2014 years. Freelancer cobid-19 because I work from home and do some projects but some I quit my job due to scammer.

6. BR (2.8 yrs)

(April, 2019 - January, 2022)

Abul khair company

Chittagong

Area of Expertise

Marketing (2.8 yrs)

Duties/Responsibilities

With 5 years of experience in Sales Marketing and Brand Representative. I started my career in Student Life and have had the opportunity to interact with people from all walks of life through Sales Marketing. I was able to put my brand in their work by understand the testimonies of the people. Understanding people's thoughts and needs by presenting the benefits and advantages of brand to them, by presenting their own practical, aspects to them. And i did present our product and got consumer everyday visit every public place, bus stand, Slum, and bazar for brand presenting that is our work.

7. Sells and marketing (1.8 yrs)

(February, 2017 - December, 2018)

Dekko food

Dhanmondi

Area of Expertise

Marketing (1.8 yrs)

Duties/Responsibilities

I had to work with wholesalers and retailers. My job was my products sell to marketers, wholesalers and retailers keeping in mind their opportunities and company profits and market demand. In addition, daily orders had to be made by Excel Sheet through computer and sent to the head office by e-mail. The main goal of my work was to increase the market. Working with new and old businesses every day was my job. The reason I quit my job at Deco Food was because I needed a 3 month break because of my exams. So I quit my job.

8. Project manager (1.9 yrs)

(January, 2015 - December, 2016)

sells development

Phantopath

Area of Expertise

Project Management (1.8 yrs)

Duties/Responsibilities

My job as a project manager was to manage an apartment project. And 12 employees worked under me. 2 gardeners 3 maids, Security guard 1 caretaker My job was to manage them and see the advantages and disadvantages of flat owners. Electricity bill, water bill, service charge, in the service had to be kept and solve any problem. By working there I have been able to fulfill my responsibilities by keeping in touch with the VIP person, the CIP person, the general driver, the general driver. By joining various meetings, my job was to raise the issue of apartments, solve economic, diplomatic and general problems and keep everyone together. My daily job was to lead 12 employees. And I always had to monitor everything with a CCTV camera. This was my first job and the reason is that my project is over. All the flats were sold, so the flats were handed over to the flat owners. And I have to wait job for 3 months for a new project. that is why i get new job so that i leave that is job.

9. Field officer (0.7 yr)

(April, 2014 - December, 2014)

Ansar VDP cooperative society

Foridgong

Area of Expertise

microfinance (0.7 yr)

Duties/Responsibilities

I did job here April ,2014 after my S.S.C Exam. As a field officer. Here, my responsibility is communication with people and collection money from them. And i gave them loan opportunity and then collection Installment to them.

Academic Qualification:

Exam Title	Concentration/Major	Institute	Result	Pas.Year	Duration	Achievement
Bachelor of Arts (BA)	English	khilgao model university	pass	2020	4	pending
HSC	Commerce	Dr. Harun or Rasid college and school	CGPA:4.08 out of 5	2016	2	А
SSC	Commerce	Rupsha High School	CGPA:4.13 out of 5	2014	2	А

Training Summary:

Training Title	Topic	Institute	Country	Location	Year	Duration
microsoft office	internet	youth club	bangladesh	Dhaka	2016	6

Professional Qualification:

Certification	Institute	Location	From	То
Data entry expert	jubo Unnayan computer proshikhan Kendro	Dhaka	February 1, 2015	March 5, 2015

Career and Application Information:

Looking For : Top Level Job Available For : Full Time

Preferred Job Category : Commercial/Supply Chain, Marketing/Sales, Media/Advertisement/Event Mgt.

Preferred District : Dhaka, Gazipur

Specialization:

Fields of Specialization	Description
 Negociation Skill Market/ Consumer Research Researcher Microsoft word and excel Microsoft PowerPoint outlook Google Sheets Video Editor International and local publisher network Mentoring and Tutoring 	All my skills are practical and practical, the means of gaining specific skills is through market research and consumer research and analyzing office policy in different corporations.

Extra Curricular Activities:

Organizing and presenting the party, presenting the presentation, and describing the presentation

Language Proficiency:

Language	Reading	Writing	Speaking
Bangla ,English, Hindi	High	High	High

Personal Details:

Father's Name : monirul Islam Mother's Name : Mohsena Date of Birth : March 2, 1998

Gender : Male

Height (Meter) : Weight (Kg) :

Marital Status : Unmarried
Nationality : Bangladeshi

Religion : Islam

Permanent Address : foridgong, Faridganj, Faridganj, Chandpur 3650

Current Location : Gazipur Blood Group : AB+